还有一个有趣的天气现象
And here's another interesting weather fact.
还有吗  太好了
Another? Great!
急流的改变可以影响
Changes in jet streams can affect the speed
地球自转的速度
at which the Earth rotates on its axis,
所以坏天气能让一天时间变得长一些
so bad weather can actually make the day longer.
那我现在一定是处于是雷电交加处
Well, there must be a hell of a storm somewhere.
随便你笑
Joke if you must,
不过你之后会想念现在的时光的
but you're going to miss these moments.
莱纳德几天后就回来了
With Leonard home in a few days,
这是你最后一次开车送我去食品店
this was your last time driving me to the grocery store.
是呀  我一定会"很"想念的
You know, I will miss this.
这样说吧  如果我买的苹果不够脆
I'll tell you what, if my apples are mealy,
我们就再杀去农产品区  来次最后的疯狂抢购
we'll hit the produce section for one last crazy blowout.
好啦  这次购物车给你推
Heck, you can even push the cart.
请别把我期盼莱纳德归来
Please don't take my looking forward to Leonard's return
当作是批评你这段时间  顶替他的工作表现
as criticism of the job you've been doing in his absence.
我不会的
I won't.
稍后送上的成绩单里会有批评的详细内容
That criticism will come later in your report card.
总之  你罚我留堂我不会理
Yeah, I didn't stay for the detention,
我也不会看成绩单
I'm not gonna read the report card.
你好
Hello.
莱纳德
Leonard!
-嘘  -你回来啦
- Shh, shh. - Hi!
-小声点  -我的天
- Keep your voice down. - Oh, my God.
你不是说周日才回来吗
You weren't supposed to be here till Sunday!
实验提前结束了
We finished the experiment early,
我就想着回家给你一个惊喜
so I thought I'd come home and surprise you.
我的天  我们为什么要这样小声说话
Oh, my gosh, why are we whispering?
我没有告诉谢尔顿
I didn't tell Sheldon,
这样我们可以过几天二人世界
so we could have a few days alone.
真是太浪漫了
Oh, that is so romantic.
当然  这正是我这么做的"理由"
Uh, sure, that's why I did it.
真不敢相信你回来了
Oh... I just cannot believe you're here.
佩妮  今天是你的幸运日
Penny, it's your lucky day!
有三个鸡蛋很明显不是特大号的
Three of the eggs are clearly not jumbo.
拿上车钥匙
Grab your keys.
人人影视
YYeTs.com
生活大爆炸
第七季  第二集
斯图尔特  请问
Uh, Stuart, I was wondering
-你能不能帮我找点东西  -非常乐意
- if you could help me find something. - Happy to,
除了帮你找希望  和活下去的理由
unless it's hope or a reason to live.
你都让我笑了  悲伤的小丑
Oh, you make me laugh, sad clown.
总之
Anyhoo...
莱纳德几天后就回来了
Leonard will be back in a couple days
我要为他准备一份欢迎回家的礼物
and I need a welcome-home gift for him.
因为他一直在海上  有可能
As he's been at sea, perhaps something
航海主题的比较合适
with a nautical theme might be appropriate.
好吧  我不知道你想花多少钱
Okay, well, I don't know how much you want to spend,
但我有个相当酷的潜水侠塑像
but I do have this pretty cool Aquaman statue.
潜水侠
Aquaman?
我不是要送恶作剧礼物  斯图尔特
Oh, this isn't a gag gift, Stuart.
没关系
Yeah, just as well.
这是相当珍贵的版本
It's a pretty rare piece.
我宁愿卖给真正的收藏家
I'd rather just sell it to a real collector.
我就是真正的收藏家
I'm a real collector.
这个有多珍贵
How rare is it?
提起这个是我不好
Oh, I shouldn't even have mentioned it.
来个蝙蝠侠水枪怎么样
How about a Batman squirt gun?
别想糊弄我买
Don't try and trick me
我根本不想买的东西
into buying something I don't want.
给我说说潜水侠
Now let's talk Aquaman.
他们在想什么呀  将章鱼博士的大脑
What were they thinking, putting Doctor Octopus's mind
放在蜘蛛侠的身体里
in Spider-Man's body?
我还挺喜欢的
Well, I've been quite enjoying that.
这样结合了《蜘蛛侠》的超级英雄乐趣
It combines all the superhero fun of Spider-Man
与《辣妈辣妹》的身体互换的恶搞
with all the body-switching shenanigans of Freaky Friday.
两个版本  都是原创加林赛·罗韩
"Both versions: original and Lohan."
你真是个白痴
You're an idiot.
你这是怎么啦
Hey, what's your problem?
对不起  最近我有些暴躁
I'm sorry, I've been kind of snippy lately.
可能因为我在减肥
It's probably this stupid diet I'm on.
你为什么要减肥
Why are you on a diet?
我胖了几磅
I've put on a couple pounds.
都得到成年男装区买裤子了
Had to buy these pants in the men's section.
我们都见过你的母亲大人
Well, we've all seen your mom.
不是一家胖人
That Butterball turkey
不进一家肥门
was bound to come home to roost.
一千二百块  不能再加了
$1,200! That's my final offer!
好吧  谢尔顿  你赢了
All right, Sheldon, you win.
我相信莱纳德一定会喜欢的
I'm sure Leonard is gonna love this.
对了  还要给莱纳德买礼物呢
Oh, right, a present for Leonard.
给我加上那把水枪吧
You better throw in that squirt gun.
你真要买吗
Yeah, I don't know.
这把水枪  相当的  相当的珍贵
This squirt gun, it's, uh, it's pretty rare.
这是我在船上做《泰坦尼克号》的招牌动作
And this is me doing the Titanic pose on the boat.
还有
And... oh.
这是我掉下船后被救起来
That's me getting rescued after I fell in.
-披萨来了  -好的
- Oh, that's the pizza. - Yep.
-给你钱  -谢谢
- Here's some money. - Thank you.
我去茅坑
And I'm gonna hit the head.
咱这些被海风吹的老练的水手
That's what us salty sea dogs say
要去尿尿时都这么说
when we have to go pee-pee.
22块5毛
$22.50.
给  25块  不用找了
Okay, here's, uh, $25. Keep the change.
不是吧
Seriously?
我刚爬了四层楼梯哦
I just walked up, like, four flights of stairs.
好吧
Okay.
给  这里有
Well, here's, um...
大概三毛钱
30-something cents
加上我向你保证不会打电话给你老板
and a promise I won't call your boss
揭发你一身大麻的臭味
and tell him you reek of marijuana.
佩妮  你点了披萨
Oh, Penny, I see you've ordered pizza.
我买了中餐回来
I have Chinese food.
真好
That's nice.
你的古龙水味好有大地的气息啊
Oh, that's a rather earthy cologne.
我叔叔以前就喷这种
My uncle used to wear that.
趁莱纳德还没有回来
Perhaps we can enjoy one last meal together
-也许我们可以共进最后一次晚餐  -多谢了
- before Leonard returns. - Yeah, thanks,
但我今晚想一个人吃饭  算了吧
but I kind of feel like eating alone tonight, so...
你确定吗
Are you sure?
你有意大利披萨  我有中式面条
With your Italian pizza and my Chinese noodles,
我们可以玩马可波罗
we could play Marco Polo.
当然了  是吃饭时
I mean, of course, a reenactment of a meal
玩威尼斯探险家马可波罗的角色扮演
in the life of Marco Polo the Venetian explorer,
不是吓死人的马可波罗水上游戏
not Marco Polo the terrifying water sport.
类似鬼抓人游戏  鬼得闭上眼睛  喊着"马克"
其他人就得喊"波罗"  听音辨位
听起来很有意思  不过多谢了
Uh, yeah, it sounds fun, but no thanks.
晚安啦
Have a good night!
你家有客人吗
What, now... do you have company?
没有  当然没有
No. No, no, no.
知道吗  马桶一直在抽风
You know what? Th-The toilet's been doing that.
我已经打电话给大厦管理员了
I called the building manager, so...
我可以帮你看看
Oh, I can take a look at it.
我对水管工的工作还挺在行的
I'm quite familiar with plumbing.
不是吹牛哈
Not to brag,
我读五年级时  大部分时候头是被摁在马桶里的
but I spent most of fifth grade with my head in a toilet.
不用了
dort dort dort Yeah, no, no, no.
谢尔顿  没关系
You know what, Sheldon, it's okay.
你不用去厕所
You don't have to go into the bathroom.
好奇怪
That's curious.
如果家里就你一个人
If there's no one here,
为什么桌上有两杯红酒
why are there two glasses of wine on the table?
这个啊
Oh.
我有两只手
Well, you know, I-I've got two hands
而且有轻微酗酒的问题
and a bit of a drinking problem.
当然了
Of course.
我问这种问题真傻
Ask a silly question.
好奇怪
That's odd.
又怎么啦
Um, what?
垃圾桶里有外带饭盒
There are takeout containers in the trash can.
有什么奇怪的  那是我昨晚的晚餐
So? That's my dinner from last night.
奇怪的是你居然把饭盒扔进垃圾桶里
What's odd is they're in the trash can.
好吧
Okay.
亲爱的  我保证这里没其他人
Look, honey, I promise there's no one's here.
我今天好累
I've had a long day.
我只想一个人安静地吃顿晚餐
I just want to have a quiet dinner by myself.
好吧
Oh, very well.
反正我早就习惯于享受独处的乐趣
I'm no stranger to enjoying the pleasures of solitude.
-对了  -什么事
- Oh! - What?
你为莱纳德准备了欢迎回家的礼物吗
Have you gotten Leonard a welcome-home gift yet?
-没有  -太好了
- No. - Oh, great.
我买了把两百块的水枪  你想跟我合送吗
Do you want to go halfsies on a $200 squirt gun?
亲爱的
Hi, honey.
我做了巧克力蛋糕  你想吃吗
I made some brownies. You want one?
你在开玩笑  对吗
You're kidding, right?
你应该知道
I mean, you know
我在减肥吧
I'm trying to lose weight.
老天  我还以为我们夫妻心有灵犀呢
God, I thought we were partners in this marriage.
我们是的  别这样
We are. Stop it.
我最后说一次  你不胖
And for the last time, you're not fat.
是吗  这话跟浴室秤说去
Really? Tell that to the bathroom scale,
你和它之间有一个在说谎
'cause one of you is lying.
好吧  当我没问
Fine, forget I asked.
在你妈妈家吃晚餐还好吗
How was dinner at your mom's?
太可怕了
Awful.
又得帮她全身擦药膏
I had to rub her ointment all over her again.
她为什么不自己擦
Why can't she do it?
因为我们母子的关系相当不健康
'Cause we've got a deeply unhealthy relationship.
这倒提醒我了
Which reminds me,
你可以趁工作之便拿这个的样品吗
do you think you can get any samples of this from work?
这个本来要用一个月的
This was supposed to last her a month,
但是医生没有考虑到
but they didn't take into account
她背部的庞大的面积
the square footage of her back.
我看看
Let me see.
你帮她擦这个多久了
How long have you been putting this on her?
不知道
I don't know.
几个星期吧  怎么啦
Few weeks. Why?
这是药效相当强的雌性激素药膏
This is really strong estrogen cream.
拜托你告诉我你戴了手套
Please tell me you've been wearing gloves.
肿得像香肠一样的手指戴得下手套吗
Like these swollen sausages could fit in gloves.
华仔  雌性激素经由你的皮肤吸收了
Howie, the estrogen's getting absorbed by your skin.
所以你最近才这么的
That's why you've been
喜怒无常  顶心顶肺
all bloated and moody and a giant pain in the ass.
你全身都是雌性激素  你怎么不这样
You're full of estrogen and you don't act like that.
因为我是女人啊
That's 'cause I'm a woman.
我练习了多年来驾驭魔性
I've had years of practice riding the dragon.
好吧
Fine.
下次我会戴手套的
I'll wear gloves next time.
这些激素要想排出体外
It's still gonna take a few weeks
还是需要几周的时间
for the hormones to leave your system.
我觉得自己好蠢
I feel so stupid.
好肥
And fat.
没关系
It's okay.
我还是觉得你好帅
You still look great to me.
不如我们去卧室
In fact, why don't we go in the bedroom
我向你证明吧
and I'll prove it to you?
上床  你不是吧
Sex? Really?
这就是你解决一切问题的方法
I mean, that's just your solution to everything!
有趣的是
Oh, and here's a fun thing.
我想到了办法  所以
I worked it out so that there are
表示勺子有两个词
two different words for spoon:
"凹里满"和"凹里空"
"Planko" and "Janko."
"凹里满"是舀了食物的勺子
"Planko" is a spoon with food,
"凹里空"是没舀食物的勺子
"Janko" is a spoon without food.
"凹里空"里的"空"要发儿话音
"Janko" is spelled with a silent "Ptang."
谢尔顿  你根本没仔细听
Sheldon, you're not even listening
我原创语言的规则
to the rules of my made-up language.
我有听啊
Yes, I am.
那么"扇扇风"是什么
Then what does "tweepadock" mean?
大象
Elephant?
算你运气好
Lucky guess.
对不起
I'm sorry.
佩妮家的事让我烦心意乱
I'm just distracted by something that happened over at Penny's.
出什么事了
What happened?
我害怕佩妮对莱纳德不忠
I fear Penny is being unfaithful to Leonard.
什么
What?
她说她是一个人
She claimed to be alone
但明明她家就还有其他的人
when there was obviously someone else in her apartment.
我往最坏的地方想也是没办法的事
I have no choice but to assume the worst,
考虑到莱纳德远航在外
given Leonard's lengthy sea voyage
还有她那声名在外的渴望被甘霖滋润的旱地
and her famously ravenous nether regions.
我觉得佩妮不会对莱纳德不忠的
I don't think Penny would cheat on Leonard.
是吗
Oh, really?
有一次我和她玩瞪眼比赛
She and I once had a staring contest.
她大声鼓掌让我眨眼
She clapped really loud and made me blink.
从这点到出轨只有一小步之遥
It's a small leap from there to sexual infidelity.
你这是在强词夺理
You're being ridiculous.
艾米  她居然会把中餐外带饭盒
Amy, there were Chinese food containers...
丢到垃圾桶里
in the trash can.
可怜的莱纳德
Poor Leonard.
你听到什么了吗
Do you hear anything?
我听到女人的声音
I hear a woman's voice.
是佩妮吗
Is it Penny?
不  是你
No, it's you.
好吧  我听到低语轻笑
All right, I hear whispering and giggling.
现在我想我听到接吻声了
Now I think I hear kissing.
说得好像你知道接吻声是什么样似的
Yeah, like you know what kissing sounds like.
《星际迷航》里有亲嘴  聪明鬼
There's kissing in Star Trek, smarty-pants.
让我听听
Let me listen.
声音像是莱纳德
Sounds like Leonard.
瞎说
Please.
为啥莱纳德提前回家
Why would Leonard come home early
却浪费时间和佩妮亲嘴
and waste his time kissing Penny
而不和他最好的朋友一起玩呢
when he could be hanging out with his best buddy?
行了  够了
Yeah, that's it.
我要去当场抓奸
I'm catching her in the act.
别  谢尔顿  别这样
No, Sheldon, don't.
抓到啦
Aha!
你这是干什么
What the hell?!
莱纳德
Leonard?
谢尔顿  你不能这样直接闯进来
Sheldon, you cannot just barge in here like that!
好吧
Right.
佩妮
Penny!
佩妮  佩妮
Penny! Penny!
你是开门呢
Are you going to answer the door
还是我自己开门  再说一次"抓到啦"
or should I open it and say "Aha" again?
抱歉  谢尔顿
I'm sorry, Sheldon.
我应该告诉你我回来了
I should've told you I was back.
我只是想和佩妮单独相处几天
I just wanted to have a couple days alone with Penny.
不  应该是我道歉
Oh, no, I should apologize.
我从未意识到我们的友谊
Uh, I never realized to what extent
对你而言是一种负担
our friendship was a burden to you.
你这么说就过分了
That is not fair.
我每月至少抱怨一次这个负担何其沉重啊
I complain about what a burden it is at least once a month.
行了行了  别绕弯子了
Oh, no, no, let's not sugarcoat this.
你就是觉得我挑剔  迂腐  讨厌嘛
You find me finicky, pedantic and annoying.
不  他没有
No, he doesn't.
我之前确实说过这些词
I actually have used those exact words before.
连顺序都一样
In that order.
莱纳德  现在是时候
Well, Leonard, I think it's high time
你我面对这房里的"扇扇风"了
you and I address the "Tweepadock" in the room.
-啥玩意儿  -艾米解释下
- The what? - Amy?
我不想掺和进来
Please leave me out of this.
好吧
Uh... fine.
莱纳德,
Leonard,
你不必
there's no need for you
再假装喜欢我了
to pretend to like me anymore.
别这样  我道歉了
Come on, I said I was sorry.
不用了  你把你的道歉
No, no, you save your apologies
留着和佩妮交媾不满意的时候用吧
for after you've had disappointing coitus with Penny.
也没很差啦
It was fine.
别这样  这太傻了
Come on, this is silly.
我这次旅行回来
Hey, um, I brought you back
给你带了礼物
a little present from my trip, huh?
是你想要的水手帽
It's that sailor cap that you wanted.
很潇洒吧
It's neat, huh?
你真觉得你用个廉价的纪念品
You honestly think you can buy back my friendship
就能赎回我们的友谊吗
with a cheap souvenir?
我没这么想
I don't.
真的  真的没这么想
No, I really don't.
试戴一下吧
Just try it on.
-赞啊  -水手你好
- Oh, yeah. - Hello, sailor.
真好看
- - Ooh, now we're talking.
失陪
Excuse me.
这顶帽子改变不了什么
This changes nothing.
不过今年的万圣节
Except the Halloween costume
我要戴这个帽子
I'm wearing this year.
艾米  你扮演奥丽弗
Amy, you're going to be Olive Oyl.
少吃点甜甜圈
Lay off the donuts.
谢谢你过来
Thanks for coming over.
不用谢
No problem.
你还做了三明治
Ooh, you made little sandwiches!
这是黄瓜奶油干酪的
Yeah, that's cucumber and cream cheese.
这是火鸡罗甘莓的
That's turkey and loganberry.
别告诉我的屁屁  但我烤箱里还热着起司呢
And don't tell my hips, but I'm warming up a brie in the oven.
不错  那...
Nice. So...
找我来什么事
Mmm. What's up?
我研究了很多关于
Okay, well, I've been reading up on all the side effects
雌性激素的副作用
you can get from estrogen,
然后...
and...
你得老实跟我说
I need you to be honest with me.
我的胸部是不是变大了
Do my boobs look bigger to you?
我看不太出来耶
Well, it's kind of hard to tell.
拉杰  你只需回答"是"或"不是"
Come on, Raj, it's a "yes or no" question.
我不确定
I'm not sure.
等等
Um, wait.
跳一跳  看你会不会乳摇
Jump up and down-- let's see if they jiggle.
不行  我...
Uh, no, I...
还是看不出来
I still can't tell, uh...
这样吧  你做这个动作
Oh, you know what? Okay, uh, give me some of this.
真的假的
Seriously?
你要不要我帮你
Do you want my help or not?
好吧
Fine.
对  对
Okay, yup.
瞧瞧  这样看起来
See, see, that-that looks like...
貌似是大了一点
that looks like they could be bigger.
不过  如果我也做同样的动作
But you know, I bet... I bet when I do it,
我也会乳摇
mine do the same thing.
是  摇得挺厉害
Yeah, they kind of do.
让我再看看
Hmm. Uh, let me see something.
嘿  别这样
Hey, easy!
我的乳头很敏感
My nipples are sensitive.
抱歉  抱歉
Sorry, sorry, uh...
好了
Okay.
我觉得...
I mean...
好像大了点
Yeah, m-maybe.
让我也摸摸
Okay, let me feel.
天啊  我肯定大了一个罩杯
No, I am definitely up a cup size.
不过你的胸部很坚挺
You know, b-but they're very firm,
所以你是捞到好处了
so you've got that going for you.
真的
You think?
是是是  非常坚挺
Yeah, yeah, yeah, very perky.
谢谢
Thank you.
今天我真的很需要鼓励
I really needed to hear that today.
-布里干酪好了  -好耶
- Ooh, brie's ready! - Yay!
-早上好  -好
- Good morning. - Hello.
要我开车送你去上班吗
So am I driving you to work
还是你要继续生我气
or are you still mad at me?
送我吧
I'd like a ride.
你真的是送我去上班就可以
Assuming you actually do take me to work.
不然我会送你去哪里
Where do you think I would take you?
谁知道
Who knows?
你说你昨天才会到家
Uh, you said you'd be home yesterday,
结果你三天前就回来了
but you came home three days ago.
你说要送我
You say you're taking me to work,
但谁知道呢
but for all I know,
没准你会把我丢在荒芜的游乐园里
I'll end up in a deserted amusement park.
或是某个玉米田迷宫
Or a cornfield maze.
或是某个后巷斗狗场
Or a back alley dog fight.
你说吧
You tell me.
我去上班了
I'm going to work.
愿意你就跟我走
You can come if you want.
好吧
Okay.
我说  你衣服上沾了脏东西
By the way, you have something on your shirt.
没有啊
No, I don't.
被人骗好伤心  对不对
Hurts, doesn't it?
我真是忍不住要怀疑
You know, I find myself wondering
你以前是不是一直在骗我
if anything you've ever told me is true.
我还是没能挽回局面
I didn't make it back.
事态严重  我是在劫难逃了
The ship sank, I'm in hell.
你说自己来自新泽西  我可不敢相信你
You say you're from New Jersey, but how can I believe you?
世界上怎么会有人冒充
Why would anyone claim to be from New Jersey
自己是新泽西人呢
if they weren't?
好吧  你说得有道理
All right, I'll give you that one.
我都道过歉了
Hey, I said I was sorry.
你还想要我怎么样啊
What else do you want from me?
-我要你承认自己错了  -行
- I want you to admit that what you did was wrong. - Fine.
我真的错了
What I did was wrong.
信你才怪
I wish I could believe you.
算了吧
You know what?
我不载你去上班了
I'm not driving you to work,
你实在是烦死人
because you're incredibly annoying.
你这人心口不一
You say one thing and do the other,
所以你不但要载我上班  还挺喜欢我的
so then you are driving me and you find me a delight.
-别说了  -继续吗
- Stop it. - Keep it up?
-再见  -你好
- Bye! - Hello!
你其实是想竖其他四根指头对吧
So I guess you're really holding up the other four fingers?
你这么早过来干什么
Oh, hey, what are you doing here so early?
送谢尔顿上班
Driving Sheldon to work.
他还在生莱纳德的气吗
He's still mad at Leonard, huh?
他也在生你的气
Well, he's mad at you, too.
他说你是让他朋友堕落的魅魔
He says you're the succubus who led his friend astray.
我不知道魅魔是什么  不过
I don't know what "Succubus" is, but...
里面有魔[烂]字  肯定不是好词
it has "suck" in it, so that can't be good.
我就觉得听到你的声音了
Thought I heard you out here.
你好呀  谢尔顿
Hey, Sheldon.
你不配我说"你好"
You don't get a "hey."
你只配得到"嗯"
You get a "hmm."
拜托  不要这么绝情
Come on, don't be like that.
我们前几个月不是一直玩得挺好的嘛
We had so much fun together the last couple of months.
你说得对
You're right.
所以你的背叛才显得更加不可饶恕
Which makes your betrayal all the more devastating.
谢尔顿
Sheldon...
我都把自己的超市会员卡
I let you buy feminine hygiene products
借给你去买女性生理用品了
with my supermarket club card.
你知道现在他们都寄给我
You have any idea the kind of coupons
什么产品的折扣券吗
I'm going to get in the mail now?
谢尔顿  你是和莱纳德斗气
Sheldon, your fight's with Leonard.
佩妮和这事没有关...
Penny's got nothing to do...
你也要小心了  艾米
Careful, Amy.
我的敌人的女友的朋友  也是我的敌人哦
The friend of my enemy's girlfriend is my enemy.
-真的吗  -是的
- Really? - Yes.
你要不就顺着我  要不就逆着我
You're either with me or against me.
我看你是打算坐公车上班了
You want to take the bus to work?
也许还存在第三种选择
Maybe there's a third option.
对了  我早餐吃的就是甜甜圈  混球
FYI, I had a doughnut for breakfast, you jerk.
现在我们还在等
So now we're just waiting for the data
船上的资料处理完毕
from the ship to be crunched,
但从数据上看  结果应该不差
but the numbers look pretty promising.
太厉害了
That's so great.
如果你们能证明盎鲁效应的存在
If you guys prove the existence of Unruh radiation...
喂  喂  这位仁兄
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
看我的眼  别乱看
My eyes are up here.
霍华德  拉杰
Howard, Raj.
犹大[背叛者]
Judas.
懒得理你
You know what?
你就是个疯子
You're a crazy person.
一个拥有好记性的疯子
A crazy person with a long memory,
如果一切进行顺利  还有一支机器人军团
and if all goes according to plan, a robot army.
别说了
Stop it.
或者是变异军团
Or a mutant army.
就看我写在圆梦网上的计划有没有人投资了
It depends on how my Kickstarter goes.
我说你们别闹了
I said, stop it!
听我说
Now, listen to me.
你们俩不光是普通朋友
You two aren't just friends.
你们可是好朋友
You're best friends.
友情是多么美好的事啊
And that's a beautiful thing.
莱纳德  你知道他为什么特别生气吗
I mean, Leonard, you know why he's so mad at you?
那是因为他想念你呀
It's 'cause he missed you!
而你作为他的好友
Yeah, and as his friend,
你应该高兴才对
you should be happy
他找到了生命中的真爱
he has love in his life.
就像我一样
As I do.
这位帅哥那天摸了我的胸部
This man held my breast the other day,
我为此深深敬爱他
and I love him for it.
你不如再吼大声点  老兄
A little loud, dude.
所以  我们能不能忽略这些小矛盾
So, can we please put aside these petty differences
为了我们的团聚开心一点
and just be glad we're here together?
-好吧  -我同意
- Okay. - I suppose so.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们没做什么怪事
Uh, it wasn't anything weird.
我是为了测量他的胸部有多大而已
It was just to see how big they were.
后来莱纳德带我去了理发店和牙医诊所
And then Leonard took me to the barber and the dentist,
以及为完美的一天划下终点的
and then to cap off the perfect day,
洛杉矶计量局
the Los Angeles Bureau of Weights and Measures.
我原以为尺寸测量最受欢迎
I thought the measures were going to be the stars of the show;
没想到重量测量更胜一筹
turns out it was the weights.
你们和好了  我真开心
I'm so glad you guys are friends again.
我俩和好了   我也很开心
And I'm glad you and I are friends again, too.
我想起来了
Aw. Which reminds me.
这是随信寄来的  我想送给你
This came in the mail, and I want you to have it.
女性阴部洗剂  凭券折价5毛
"50 cents off Vagisil."
使用的时候可别忘了我
Think of me when you apply it.
我想对你们说
Uh, can I just say,
我真心怀念大家伙聚在一起的时光
I've missed all of us hanging out together.
-没错  -我也是
- Yeah. - Me, too.
库斯拉帕从什么时候开始
Um, since when can Koothrappali talk
不用喝酒也可以在女生面前讲话啦
in front of the girls without a beer?
你刚走他就痊愈了
Oh, that happened right after you left.
怎么没人告诉我
And no one told me?
我们居然忘记告诉他了
Can't believe we forgot to tell him.
使用的时候别忘了谢尔顿
Think of Sheldon when you apply it.